DAVID KELVY **TOMALA CIMARRA**

Santo Domingo · +593 990511926 kelvydavid.92@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/davidkelvy

Professional Profile

An Electromechanical Engineer with experience in the design and construction of distribution grids, as well as the implementation of Geographic Information Systems (GIS). His technical background is complemented by studies in Engineering in Information Technologies, which enables him to integrate innovative solutions in infrastructure and technology system management. His professional profile is characterized by a constant drive for process improvement and optimization, supported by a proactive approach and a passion for technology. His goal is to continue developing technical and management skills in multidisciplinary projects, contributing to the growth of organizations through the implementation of efficient, high-impact solutions, while expanding his knowledge in emerging fields of engineering and technology.

Education

ELECTROMECHANICAL ENGINEER | JUNE 2019 | UTE UNIVERSITY

Reg. SENESCYT No. 1032-2019-2094258

CERTIFICATION IN OCCUPATIONAL RISK PREVENTION: ELECTRICAL ENERGY | SEPTEMBER 2022 | GRUPOGESTIONA S.A.

Reg. SETEC No. MDT-480-CCL-368184

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ENGINEERING | IN PROGRESS | UNEMI

Fourth semester (in progress)

Training

- · SCREEN PROGRAMMING HMI-KINCO | OCTOBER 2022 | 40 hours
- · ELECTRICAL CONTROL AND INDUSTRIAL AUTOMATION | NOVEMBER 2018 | 40 hours
- PUBLIC PROCUREMENTS DIRECTED TO SUPPLIERS | SEPTEMBER 2018 | 40 hours
- · GEOGRAPHICAL INFORMATION SYSTEMS AND THE USE OF ARCGIS | APRIL 2018 | 40 hours
- · INDUSTRIAL MAINTENANCE MANAGEMENT | MARCH 2018 | 40 hours
- ELECTRICAL RISKS PREVENTION | JANUARY 2018 | 40 hours

Experience

GIS PROFESSIONAL | VILLAVICENCIO CE | JULY 2024 - PRESENT

- · Update and Validation of Data Quality of Geographic Information Systems (GIS)
- · GIS process automation

ELECTROMECHANICAL ENGINEER | SMART ENERGY | JUNE 2018 - PRESENT

- · Administration, supervision and engineering of electrical projects (Distribution grids)
- · Control and automation project engineering
- · Update and Validation of Data Quality of Geographic Information Systems (GIS)
- · GIS process automation

GIS PROFESSIONAL | BLUE LINE ENERGY | OCTOBER 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- · Update of Geographic Information Systems (GIS)
- · Preparation of thematic maps

ASSISTANT/ DIGITATOR | INSELECTRIC | JULY 2017 - FEBRUARY 2018

- · Engineering of electrical projects (Distribution grids)
- · Information gathering for electrical projects

PROJECT ASSISTANT | SD ENERGÍA | APRIL 2016 - DECEMBER 2016

- Engineering of electrical projects (Distribution grids)
- · Conventional and remote measurement systems

ELECTROMECHANICAL TECHNICIAN | R ELECTRIC | AUGUST 2014 - MARCH 2017

- · Control and automation project engineering
- · Engineering of electrical projects

Aptitudes and abilities

- · MS Office utility package
- · CAD/CAM/CAE software
- · Geographic Information Systems
- · Database administration
- · Studies and design of distribution grids
- · HMI, PLC, Drives, etc. programming.
- · Lighting design
- · Home automation
- · Industrial maintenance management
- · Electromechanical project management
- · Information technology
- · SCADA
- · Leadership
- · Teamwork
- · AutoCAD
- · CYMDIST
- · ArcGIS
- · Analysis and resolution of problems
- · English and Spanish
- · Python, SQL, Java, etc.